Original Work
Gosei Furukawa
(Serialized in Kodansha's "Monthly Shounen Magazine R")
Where am I?
I woke up
Starting today, you're my pet.
and became a
dog
of the girl I like
Whaaaaaaaaaat?!
Pochita
VA:  Shuuichirou   Umeda
Morning walks are fun. Right, Pochita?
Karen Inukai
VA:  Saya   Aizawa
Mike Nekotani
VA:  Mayu   Sagara
Don't come any closer!
Usagi Tsukishiro
Senpai is always alone.
Isn't this the first time we talked?
VA:  Yurie   Kozakai
Everything around me is so much bigger than me.
Starting today, you are Pochita.
Low angle
DOG'S POV
Original romcom idea
Back then, when I was a human,
I couldn't even touch her hand.
After becoming a dog,
I can finally hold Inukai-san's hand.
Broadcasting begins in January 2023
My Life as Inukai-san's Dog.
Broadcasting begins in January 2023.
Pochita
Umeda Shuuichirou
Karen Inukai
Saya Aizawa
Mike Nekotani
Mayu Sagara
Usagi Tsukihiro
Yurie Kozakai
Pochita
Umeda Shuuichirou
Karen Inukai
Saya Aizawa
Mike Nekotani
Mayu Sagara
Usagi Tsukihiro
Yurie Kozakai
GEO
(typesetting)
QAC
(quality control)
NATSUHARU
(translation)
website
twitter
#inuhiro